

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

C, C#, Java, Python, PHP, Matlab

Frameworks/Systems

Deep Learning

- TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Data Science

- NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Seaborn, Scikit-Learn

Others

- Ruby on Rails, Laravel

COURSES

- Neural Networks and Deep Learning/ Coursera
- Al for Everyone/Coursera
- Machine Learning Crash Course/Google Developers
- Signal and Image Processing, Deep Learning/ TED University
- Database Design and Programming with SOL/ORACLE
- Machine Learning, Deep Learning/IEEE TURKEY SECTION
- Radar Systems Fundamentals/ASELSAN
- DATALTEAM
 - Statistics & Python: Basic Statistics Science
- Deep Learning and Python: Deep Learning
- Machine Learning and Python
- Data Visualization
- -Data Science and Python: Expertise

CONTACT

+90 544 416 35 35

in linkedin.com/in/elifmeseci/

github.com/elifmeseci

k kaggle.com/elifmeseci

REFERENCES

Assist. Prof. Caner OZCAN CEO, Founder of SimurgAl

+90 (370) 418 7050

canerozcan@karabuk.edu.tr

ELIF MESECI

Computer Engineer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I completed my bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering Department at Karabuk University. I have been working as an Artificial Intelligence Developer at SimurgAI, located in the Technology Development Office of Karabuk University. I have a researcher, harmonious personality with strong problem-solving skills and high communication skills.

EDUCATION

KARABUK UNIVERSITY (GPA-3.04 / 4.00)

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | 2016 - 2021

- Computer Engineering Department (100% English)

EXPERIENCE

AI DEVELOPER

SimurgAI | Nov 2020-

 Object Detection, Segmentation and Analysis on MR Images via Transfer Learning

SUMMER INTERN

Karabuk University | Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

- Data Science, Data Analysis
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

LABORATORY ASSISTANT

Karabuk University | Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

• Student Assistant of CME112-Programming Languages Course

PROJECTS

ANALYSIS OF PANORAMIC DENTAL IMAGES USING ARTIFICIAL LEARNING TECHNIQUES

SimurgAI | 2020- 2021

• Mask RCNN, Faster RCNN, ResNet

SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTO ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK R-CNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

SimurgAI | 2020 - 2021

• Mask RCNN. ResNet

CLASSIFICATION OF WRIST IMAGES WITH DEEP LEARNING MODELS

Medathon | 2021

• VGG, AlexNet, ResNet, Tranfer Learning

PAPERS

TOOTH DETECTION AND NUMBERING WITH INSTANCE SEGMENTATION IN PANORAMIC RADIOGRAPHS

ICIDAAI

SEGMENTATION OF BITEWING INTO ORAL X-RAY IMAGES WITH MASK R-CNN DEEP LEARNING MODEL

II.International Artificial Intelligence in Health Congress 2021